nice to meet you.
初めまして
初 めまして
It's so cute, really.
可愛いですね、めちゃめちゃ
Your smile is wonderful.
笑顔が素敵ですね
Isn't that often said?
よく言われないですか?
Not told.
言われない
The cameras are rolling, are you nervous?
カメラ回ってますけど、緊張してますか?
yes.
はい
What do you usually do?
普段、何されてるの?
I'm a university student.
大学生です
I'm a student.
学生さんなんだ
You're young.
若いですね
What year is it now?
今何年のの?
I'm a first year student.
1年生です
1 year?
1年?
So, in terms of age?
ってことは、年齢的に言うと?
It's 19.
19です
It's perfect.
ピチピチだね
If you were 19, I'm quite a bit older than you.
19だったらさ、 俺結構、歳離れてるんだけど、
What was your first cell phone?
初めて持った携帯って何?
iPhone8
Seriously?
マジ?
Is it 8?
8なの?
first time?
初?
That's right.
そうだわ
I'm a pattern person.
俺、柄系なよ
Do you know the one that snaps?
パカパカするやつ、知ってる?
Do you know about OneSev?
ワンセブとかって知ってる?
I don't know.
わかんない
A long time ago, there was a cell phone that had a radio wave-like stick extending out from it.
昔、携帯から、 電波みたいな棒がビヨーンって伸びる携帯があ
That's how I was picking up the radio waves.
って、 それで電波拾ってたんだ
He's playing a little bit.
ちょっと弾いてるじゃん
There might be a little more generation cap, though.
もうちょっとジェネレーションキャップあるかもしれないけど、
By the way, since you are a student,
学 生さんってことで、 ちなみになんだけど、
Can you say the school name?
学校名とか言えたりする?
Is it tough?
厳しいかな?
I don't know if you understand, but I don't drink tea.
分かるか分かんないけど、 お茶飲みずって、
Do you know?
知ってる?
It's extremely famous.
めちゃめちゃ有名っすよ
I feel humble.
謙遜入りましたね
Isn't it very famous?
めっちゃ有名じゃないですか
It's a women's university.
女子大だよね
Women's college.
女子大
Is it a department or faculty?
学科とか学部かな?
Faculty of Science.
理学部
It's a science major.
理系なんすね
Yeah.
うん
wise.
賢い
No, no.
違う違う
Looks smart.
賢そう
Do you like supermarkets?
スーパーとか好きなの?
like.
好き
Sine, cosine?
サイン、コサイン?
Tancento.
タンチェント
I see.
分かるね
Sine, cosine, tancento.
サイン、コサイン、タンチェント
Is there something like this?
こういうのある?
Is it like this?
こういうの?
Is there a way to say this?
こう いうのある?
root?
ルート?
It's science.
理系だね
It's a little low level though.
ちょっとレベル低いけどね
Are you currently involved in any sports or clubs?
今なんかスポーツとか、 サークルかやってるの?
I'm running track and field.
陸上してる
land?
陸上?
It's a hurdle, right?
ハードルでしょ
Long distance.
長距離
Long distance?
長距離?
Like, how far do you run?
なんか、どれくらい走るの?
Like long distance.
長距離とかって
I run a lot, like 3km or 1.5km.
3キロとか、 1.5キロとか、 いっぱい走る
Do you run a full marathon?
フルマラソンとか走ったりするの?
42.1 km.
42.1キロ
62.64 points.
62.64点が
I'm going to die.
死ぬね
I'm so frustrated.
悔しすぎる
Do you do some sort of marathon?
なんかそういうマラソンとかも やったりするの?
It's like a full marathon.
フルマラソンみたいな
Do you have any thoughts?
感想しようとある?
Seriously?
マジ?
Is this rule marathon your dream?
夢はこのルールマラソン?
What is that?
何それ?
i don't know?
知らない?
This rule.
このルール
Got it.
分かった
Certainly.
確かにね
Those legs look like they could be used for long distances.
長距離やってそうな 足だよね
thin.
細い
It's insanely thin.
めちゃめちゃ細い
Can I give you a little update?
ちょっとアップデートさせていい?
feet.
足
thin.
細い
Can I stretch my legs for once?
一回足伸ばしてもらっていい?
Can you run with those legs?
そんな足で走れんの?
Since when have you been doing this?
いつ頃からやってるんですか?
Since elementary school.
もう小学校の時から
Elementary school or something.
小学校とか
Have you been doing this for a long time?
ずっとやってるんですか?
I've been doing it for a long time.
ずっとやってる
Does your family have that kind of finances?
家がそういう家計とか?
I feel like I want it to be normal.
普通にしたいな、みたいな
And it continues.
で、続いてるんだ
nice.
いいね
I guess in the future I'd like to become a famous player like that.
なんか そういう、将来的には やっぱそういう 有名な選手に行
Is there something like that?
った りとか そういうのもありますか?
Yeah.
うん
yes.
はい
It's definitely a lie, right?
絶対嘘でしょ?
Do you want to continue doing track and field in the future?
陸上とかは 将来続けていたいと思ってんの?
I want to continue, but...
続けたい、でも
I'm rooting for you.
応援してるんで
Well then, next time I'll go to Ochanomizu to cheer on the school.
じゃあ、今度 お茶の水だけ 学校に応援しに行くね
please.
お願いします
Did you ask for it?
お願いされた?
I'm going, really.
行っちゃうよ、本当に
Can I go to a cultural festival?
文化祭とか行っていい?
please.
どうぞ
Is there still a school festival or something?
文化祭とか、 まだあれか、ないのか?
Have you never done it?
や ったことないのか?
What do you want to do?
どういうことしたいとかあるの?
I want to open a food stall.
屋台出したい
Jaguar butter?
ジャガーバターとか?
Jaguar butter.
ジャガーバター
What kind of stall would you like to open?
何の屋台出したい?
What stall?
何の屋台?
Like Ichigaume.
いちがうめとか
cute.
かわいい
It's sparkling.
キラキラじゃん
Do you have a boyfriend now?
今、彼氏とかいるの?
not present.
いない
How long have you been gone?
どれくらいいない?
About 3 years.
3年とか
There aren't quite a lot of them.
結構いないんで
Even though it's this cute?
こんなかわいいのに?
It really exists, right?
本当にいるでしょ?
not present.
いない
Isn't there?
いないですか?
Seriously?
マジ?
So, the last person you dated was Koichi or something like that?
じゃあ、最後に付き合ったのは、 コウイチとかそれくらいのな?
How long did you and the person you were dating last?
お前さ、 付き合った人はさ、 どれくらい続いたの?
It didn't last that long, like half a year.
そんな続いてなくて、 半年とか
That's right.
そっかそっか
Is it quite short?
結構短めなのか
Only that person?
その人だけ?
Only that person.
その人だけ
Seriously?
マジ?
Is that so?
そうなの?
What was that person like?
そんな人はどういう感じの人だったの?
I was familiar with it as an adult, and I really liked it.
大人馴染みで、 めっちゃ好きだった
Familiar with adults?
大 人馴染み?
Somehow, even though I'm an adult, I don't have the image of going all the way to marriage.
なんか、大人馴染みってもう、 結婚まで行くイメージじゃない
But I found out it was only half a year.
けど、 半年と分かっちゃった
Because it’s born?
生まれるから?
I tore the frame.
枠裂いちゃった
Did you tear the frame?
枠裂いちゃった?
I see.
そっか
Ma, ma, ma, imitate.
ま、ま、ま、まね
Then darkness doesn't get angry, darkness doesn't get angry.
じゃあ、闇は怒らないし、闇は怒らない
That's right.
そっかそっか
What kind of person is your type?
どういう人がタイプなの?
kind person.
優しい人
How does it look?
見た目とかは?
I've never really cared about looks.
見た目とかは、あんま気にしたことない
I don't care.
気にしない
What type of person do you like?
好きな人タイプ?
Yeah.
うん
School is all about girls.
学校、女子なりだもんね
We'll never meet again.
出会い、いずれないよね
Isn't there a blind date?
合コンとかないの?
It's a boys' school, or rather, it's like a point of contact with education.
男子校、というか、教学との接点みたいな
Not much, I guess.
ないかな、あんまり
Well, I'll do it.
まあ、俺がやるもんな
picture?
え?
It's not quite right.
あんま違うと
I scratched it in my heart.
心に削ったんすけど
Do you have any hobbies?
趣味とかあるの?
My hobby is watching baseball games.
趣味は、 野球観戦好き
I like watching baseball games.
野球観戦好きなんだ
Mets?
メッツ?
picture?
え?
Dodgers?
ドジャース?
High school baseball.
高校野球
Ah, high school baseball.
あ、高校野球
It's not a major.
メジャーじゃないんだ
Exactly.
あ んまね
What makes you happy about high school baseball?
高校野球、どこが嬉しいの?
Well, it's a secret.
うーん、秘密で
secret?
秘 密?
It's such a secret.
そんな秘密なんだ
I see.
そ っか
What's good?
何がいいの?
High school baseball.
高校野球
Tell me about your charm.
魅力を教えて
hot.
暑い
hot?
暑い?
Oh, I see, I also play sports.
あ、そうか、自分もスポーツやってるもんね
I kind of like the sports-like heat.
なんか、スポーツ的な暑さが 好きなんだ
like.
好き
Surprisingly, I'm quite an active outdoors person.
意外に結構アクティブな アウトドア派なんだ
What do you do on your day off?
お休みの日何してる?
On my days off, I like to make sweets.
お休みの日は、 お菓子作りとか
Oh, seriously?
お、マジ?
Are you making sweets?
お菓子作りしてるの?
What are you going to make?
何作るの?
Jacques Golantin?
ジャック・ゴランタン?
Well, even if it's difficult.
あれ、難しいでも
You might be able to make pretty much anything.
結構何でも作れるかも
What did you make recently?
直近で、 何作った?
Make gateau chocolate well.
ガトー・ショコラうまく作る
It's pretty serious.
結構ガチだね
Cookies, I thought.
クッキーとか、 俺の思ったけど
I made gateau chocolate.
ガトー・ショコラ作った
What was it made for?
それは何用に作ったの?
I don't like it when someone I like asks me to do it.
好きな人が申してきたら嫌よ
I see.
そうか
I didn't listen to it much.
あんまり聞かなかった
Nice, cute.
いいね、かわいい
I'm making sweets.
お菓子作りなんだ
Well, I made it this time.
じゃあ、今度作ったよ
Well then, don't give me gateau chocolat.
じゃあ、俺にはガトー・ショコラくれない
I'll think about it.
考えてきます
That outfit is stylish.
おしゃれですね、その服
Hey Minnie.
ちょっとミニー
Minnie skirt.
ミニースカート
It's a little Minnie.
ちょっとミニーだね
Do you usually wear clothes like this?
普段、こういう服装多いの?
There may be many.
多いかも
I like it, he looks like a student and like a holy ancestor.
いいね、学生っぽくて、 聖祖みたいな感じ
It's Minnie.
ミニーだね
Is this okay?
これ大丈夫?
Can you see it?
見えちゃう?
yeah?
ん?
If this fluttering, do it like this.
これ、ひらひらーってきたらさ、 こうやって
Sorry.
すいません
Like this.
こうやって
This is fluttering
これ、 ひらひらー
That's it.
って
Because it's cute.
か わいいからさ
I looked closely, could you please stand up?
よく見たんだけど、 立ち上がってもらっていい?
That's nice, it's cute.
いいですね、かわいいですね
In a small island village.
ちっちゃいしまむらで
So, you hate me?
あれ、俺のこと嫌い?
Please give me a little peace.
なんか、ちょっとピースとかしてよ
No.
いやい
Please turn your back
後ろ、向いてもらえ
do not have?
ない?
You might be able to see some panties.
ちょっと パンツ見えてるかも
You'll definitely get scoffed at.
絶対なんか、チカンとかされるよ
Like this.
こんな 感じで
Won't you get pissed off like this?
こんな感じで、チカンとかされない?
Are you ready for this?
これの準備大丈夫?
Trap?
わな?
Come on, I'll get ready too.
ちょっとさ、俺も準備してくるからさ
Can I have you mentally prepared?
心の準備しといてもらっていい?
Are you mentally prepared?
心の準備は?
Are you more nervous than before?
さっきより緊張してない?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
dislike?
嫌い?
Don't you hate it?
嫌いじゃない?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Just sit here and take a nap,
ちょっとさ、ここに 朝寝に座ってさ、
Peace?
ピ ースする?
The size of your face is small.
顔の大きさが、ちっちゃいね顔ね
It's so tiny.
めちゃめちゃちっちゃいね
How many centimeters is your face?
何センチ顔?
How many centimeters?
何センチ?
How many acorns?
どんぐり何個分?
3個
This is terrible.
やばいよ
Three acorns like this?
こんなにどんぐり3個?
Is it visible?
映ってる?
Can you see the house?
家映ってます?
It's cute.
可愛いですね
So, you've only had a boyfriend who's familiar with dishes so far.
じゃあ彼氏が 今までお皿なじみと 一人ですね
Honestly, should I lose?
正 直その 負けていいのかな?
No.
ダメ
Are you going to meet a woman?
女にとかってすんの?
picture?
え?
do not?
しない?
Just play a little bit.
ちょっと弾いてんじゃん
Can't count the number of people with experience?
経験人数できない?
1 person.
1人
How many times?
何回くらい?
3 times in my life so far.
今まで人生3回
Have you ever had a channel like that?
そんなチャンネルしたことない?
So, is this the first time you've ever had a camera roll?
じゃあカメラ回って みたいなのも初?
I'll do it, but is it okay?
しちゃうけど 大丈夫?
It's cute.
可愛いね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
I thought I was being yelled at now.
叫ばれてると思った今
cute.
可愛い
So cute.
めっちゃ可愛い
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
Yeah.
うん
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
Yeah.
うん
Look at me now, cue, head towards me.
今のこっち見てさ、キューって向かって グイーンって
First time in 3 years?
3年ぶりの?
Yeah.
うん
Yeah?
うん?
a,
あ、
Hey, it's just too cute. I'm starting to react a little bit more.
ちょっと もうさ 可愛すぎてさ もうちょっとなんか反応してき
That's it, like this.
ちゃ ったね こうやって
This is how I reacted.
こうやってちょっと反応してきたね
Look, look, like this.
見て見て、こうやって
I've had a little reaction.
ちょっと反応してきた
You're playing it.
弾いてんじゃん
It's long.
長いな
The bottom line?
下の線?
Can't get it out?
出せない?
picture?
え?
Can't get it out?
出せない?
That's fine.
それいいよ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
I don't remember.
覚えてない
Don't you remember?
覚えてない?
I don't remember.
覚えてない
Don't you remember?
覚えてない?
Here, I'm called Goron.
ここでさ ゴローンってして
Start dancing.
踊りかかって
It was cute, but it was embarrassing.
可愛いな、恥ずかしかった
Stretch your legs.
足伸ばして
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I can already see it, but just a little.
もう見えてるけどね、ちょっと
picture?
え?
It makes me want to be mean.
意 地悪したくなっちゃうね
I can see it though.
見えてるけどね
Just for a moment, open it yourself.
一瞬だけさ 自分で開いてよ
picture?
え?
No?
ダメ?
Well then, let's play rock, paper, scissors.
じゃ、じゃんけんしよう
I didn't cut it well.
俺はカットダメしてね
At first it was rock, paper, scissors.
最初は じゃんけんほい
It's Aiko.
あいこでしょい
Okay.
よし
Just for a moment.
一瞬だけ
I close my eyes
俺目つぶっとく
Yo.
よ
It's nice, it's cute, it's embarrassing.
いい ね、可愛いね、恥ずかしい
I've never seen it before.
全然見られたことないんだもんね
Is that still no good?
そこはまだダメ?
Is this okay?
こっちならいい?
Can I see it?
見ていい?
Well then, let's play rock, paper, scissors again.
じゃあ、もう一回じゃんけんしようか
From the beginning.
最初から
picture?
え?
You won at rock, paper, scissors.
じゃんけん勝ったじゃん
No.
ダメ
why?
なんで?
I won at rock, paper, scissors, so I wanted to see it again.
じゃんけん勝ったから あと見たいなって
It's over.
終 わった
Well then, please join me.
じゃあ、一緒のお願い
Should I use it here?
ここで使うかな?
Please join me.
一緒のお願い
It's like a game.
ゲームみたい
I won at rock, paper, scissors, so that's amazing.
じゃんけん勝ったから すごいやっぱりね
Just flip up your pants yourself.
自分でさ、パンツとかこうやってめくって
Turn up your pants or skirt.
パンツとかスカートめくって
please.
お願いします
I even used it to ask for the same thing.
一緒のお願いだって使ったんだもんね
difficult.
難しい
Touch it yourself.
自分で触ってにするの
Well then, I think my current state is embarrassing.
じゃあ、今の状態が恥ずかしいと思うから
Because it's half-baked.
中途半端だから
Are you taking this off?
これ脱ごっか
Probably because it's the most embarrassing thing to do half-heartedly.
中途半端が一番恥ずかしいから、多分
Because being half-hearted is the most embarrassing thing.
中途半端が一番恥ずかしいから
I'm thin.
うち細いね
Try Garshan.
ガーシャンしてみて
It's been quite a while.
もうだいぶ
yeah?
ん?
Look at this white arm.
腕のこの白さを見てみて
It has to tickle me.
くすぐるよじゃないと
I'll tickle you if you don't show me.
見せてくれないとくすぐるよ
lie?
嘘?
So let's play rock, paper, scissors again?
じゃあもう一回じゃんけんする?
Play rock, paper, scissors and win or lose.
じゃんけんして勝ち負け
Should I show it to you with rock-paper-scissors, or should I force myself to show it to you?
じゃんけんで見せるか、もう俺無理やり見せるか
I'm guessing the options by playing rock, paper, scissors.
一応じゃんけんで選択肢を当ててるからね
From the beginning.
最 初から
You're learning.
学習してるね
Let's start here.
最初はここでいこう
From the beginning.
最初から
As expected from science.
さすが理系
I'm reading ahead.
先読んでる
I like your head.
頭いいね
I'm surprised now.
びっくりした今
But let's really do it.
でも本当にやろう
Let's really do it.
本当にやろう
At first, it was rock-paper-scissors.
最初はグー、じゃんけんおい
Then I lost a bit, so it was the second round.
じゃあ次ちょっと負けたんで、第二ラウンド
Should I show you if I'm tickling?
くすぐりか見せるか
No way.
やだ
Either one or the other.
どっちかどっちか
show.
見せる
Because I said so.
言ったからね
I'm already feeling better.
俺もう元気取ったからね
Well, let me show you a little bit.
じゃあちょっと見せて
Show me both.
両方見せて
Until you say okay.
いいって言うといいって言うまで
Okay, 3 seconds.
じゃあ3秒
I'll count.
俺が数える
Do it again.
もう一回やって
That's right.
当たってるよ
当 たってるよ
Show me again.
もう一回見せて
Open your eyes again.
もう一回目を開けて
No more.
もうダメ
Sorry, sorry.
ごめんごめん
Well then, one more time.
じゃあもう一回
Won it.
当たれて
Because I won't do it anymore.
もうしないから
It's this one.
こっちの方ですね
Because I can clearly see it.
あんま見えてるから
nice.
いいね
Your face looks dark.
顔かくなってるね
Because it doesn't tickle, it doesn't tickle.
くすぐんないくすぐんないから
Just look, just look.
見るだけ見るだけ
yes.
はい
I'm already scared.
もう恐怖
You're heartless.
心情ないじゃん
Which one is better?
どっちがいい?
こっちそのどっちがいい?
If you shy away from me, I'll only become even more mean.
恥ずかしがってくれると 余計に意地悪くなっちゃうだけなんだ
Yo.
よ
Okay.
いい よ
That's fine there.
そこでいいよ
Here, just a little more.
ここでさ、もうちょっとさ
here
ここ
Why is it not good?
は なんでダメなの?
I didn't take a picture there.
そこ撮ってないよ
Are you okay.
大丈夫
It's not shown there.
そこ映ってない
It's not shown.
映ってないよ
There.
そこ
It was ruined.
ダメされたね
Lean on it and spread your legs.
そこに元にかかって 足広げて
Can the legs be made into an M-shape?
足M字化できる?
It's embarrassing if you look at it from the front.
前から見たら恥ずかしいからさ
So, let's take a secret photo here.
そこでさ、 ここで秘術で撮る
So, my feet are on the sofa.
で、ソファーの上に 足
It's not embarrassing, right?
恥ずかしくないでしょ?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Look here from the left.
左からこっち見て
Sorry, sorry.
ごめん、ごめん
Easy to take care of.
大切に流しやすい
Show me, show me.
見せて、見せて
please.
お願い
Really please.
本当にお願い
No.
ダメ
Now, the opposite cloth part.
じゃあ、逆の布の部分
Only the front, not the back.
裏面じゃなくて表面だけ
Show me just the surface.
表面だけ見せて
picture?
え?
That's not the surface, right?
そこ、表面じゃないでしょ?
Really, really.
ほんとに、ほんとに
Believe me.
信じてくれよ
It's so cute, I'm getting excited.
かわいすぎてさ、 興奮してきたからさ、
With your feet, you know?
足でさ、 分かる?
Even with your feet.
足でも
Leave this.
これ残して
Wait, what?
ちょっと、 え?
No, I thought it was over here.
いや、こっち向こうと思って
what?
なに?
Well then, it's mine, my bottom, my pussy.
じゃあさ、 自分のさ、 下、おまんこさ、
Let me spread it out.
広げてみせて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Put your hands under your feet,
自分の手をさ、 足の下に回してさ、
Spread it out.
広げて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
please.
お願いします
Please join me.
一緒のお願い
I just asked you to join me.
さっき一緒のお願い聞いたよ
Because they didn't accept that,
あれなんかね、 受け付けてくれなかったから、
It wasn't removed, so I'll try a little more this time.
除去されなかったんで、 今回ちょっと、
I think I'll use a real request.
本当のお願いを 使おうかなと
So, with your hands, spread it out.
それで、自分の手でね、 広げて
end?
終わり?
please.
お願いします
I bow my head.
頭さげるんで
Spread it out until you say it's okay.
いいって言うまで広げといてね
Until you say okay.
いいって言うまで
Next time I make a suggestion, I'll look at your pants.
次提発したら、 パンツ見るからね
Have you ever seen it yourself?
自分でさ、 見たことある?
Did you see your body position?
自分の体の位置見たか?
What do you say?
なんて言うの?
I don't know.
わかんない
So let's watch and remember.
じゃあ見て覚えようか
Since I let go, I'm wearing pants.
手離したから、 パンツパンツ
pants?
パンツ?
It's pants.
パンツだよ
So can you show me?
じゃあ見せてくれる?
Can you show me one more time?
もう 一回見せてくれる?
Please show me all the things I do well.
私のうまくいっぱい見せてくださいって
please.
お願いします
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
myself.
自分
what up?
どうした?
That hand is cute.
かわいい、その手
Is it better to put your finger in?
指入れてる方がいい?
Is it better not to put my finger in?
指入れん方がいいの?
Well then, I thought it was embarrassing.
じゃあさ、 恥ずかしいと思ってさ、
Can I hold you here again?
ここにもう一回、 持たれかかっていい?
Should I rest my elbows there?
そこで肘ついておく?
what up?
どうした?
muff
マフ
Laa, can you put it over there?
ラ ーそっちに置いてくれる?
Get on your elbows.
肘ついて
Drop it.
落として
what up?
どうした?
Let me touch you.
触らせて
It's so rough
すげーザラザラして
Ru.
る
refers to weak
指 弱
stomach?
い?
What about your left hand even though it's your right hand?
右 手ながら、 左手は?
You can do it by hand, right?
手でいけるでしょ?
It hurts, are you okay?
痛 い、大丈夫?
Let's take a short break and lick it.
ちょっと下を休憩で、 舐めていこう
It's cute.
かわいいね
He's a sensitive person.
敏感者だ